[Fate Chooses You]
[Episode 37]
Miss Xin,
we are about to begin.
Please excuse yourself.
Rest assured.
Did everything go smoothly on Lu's side?
When he wakes up,
everything will be over.
September 9th,
the Double Ninth Festival.
Today is your birthday.
No,
today is the birthday
of all Heavenly Talents.
I even saved one for Sheng
to eat when she comes back.
Eating the egg
will bless us
with smooth sailing
and longevity.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
What else?
We're going together.
Don't be ridiculous.
Do you know what place that is?
What?
You think we are not strong enough
to go along?
Don't forget,
you used to be
our defeated opponent.
You're going anyway too, aren't you?
You didn't have to bring that up...
This matter is of great importance.
We can't act impulsively.
That's exactly why
we have to go.
This matter
doesn't just concern your immortal sect.
Exactly.
That old fool of the Tianyuan Sect
wants to become an immortal
by taking the lives of
half the world's population.
The 3 of us have been
peacefully tending to our shop,
and now half of us might die?
No way.
Stop talking nonsense
and let's set off.
Junior, you're quite late.
-Master.
-Thank you for waiting.
Junior and I were drawing the map
and forgot the time.
Do you have any ideas?
For this attack on the mountain,
we will split into 2 teams.
The first team
will attack through the main gate
and head straight
for the Rainwatch Terrace.
This is where the sacred seed
of the Jianmu Tree is located.
If nothing unexpected happens,
all the elite disciples of Tianyuan Sect
will be waiting here.
The second team
will take the mountain path
to Qingtian Peak.
Qingtian Peak?
What's the use of going to Qingtian Peak?
What you don't know is that
my sect's sacred object,
the Infinity Bell,
is right at the top of Qingtian Peak.
The Infinity Bell is the key to activating
the Mountain-Guarding Formation.
Once the formation is activated,
Tianyuan Mountain will be
isolated from the world.
By then, even if the Jianmu Tree matures,
it won't be able
to break through the formation
and absorb the vitality from the outside.
Since Li Mofu
has already entered
the realm of Deity Transformation,
let me
take him on.
I will go with Sect Master Lin
and attack from the main gate.
I'll go too.
I'll take the mountain path.
But this Dingyuan Infinity Bell
can only be rung by
a Nascent Soul cultivator.
So,
Daoist Master Gong Yu,
please come with me.
Of course.
I will go with Senior Bai, too.
Ji,
protect yourself well.
Master.
Take this.
The Eight-Treasure
Heart-Protecting Mirror.
This is Lingji Mountain's
ultimate treasure.
It is impervious to water and fire,
and basically indestructible.
Ji,
this is a dowry
from your Master
to you.
Who else hasn't arrived?
Besides the fallen immortal sects,
only those from Zigai Mountain,
Posuo Sect,
and Tianyin Mountain are missing.
I wonder if those from Tianyin Mountain
will even show up.
What time is it?
It is almost a quarter past the Mao hour.
There is still half an hour
until the agreed time.
Start the timer.
[Li Mofu, I’ve led the disciples
to gather at the foot of the mountain.]
[If the sacred seed is not destroyed within
half an hour, we will storm Tianyuan Sect.]
Reporting to the Sect Leader,
all the major immortal sects
have gathered at the foot
of Tianyuan Mountain.
Members of Zigai Mountain, Posuo Sect,
and Tianyin Mountain have not yet arrived.
Lin An has sent a declaration of war.
If we don't destroy
the sacred seed of the Jianmu Tree,
in half an hour,
they will attack the mountain.
Sect Leader,
are we going to accelerate the growth
of the sacred seed today?
Accelerating the growth
of the divine Jianmu Tree
will drain the life force
of half the living creatures in the world.
If we are not absolutely certain,
I am afraid...
Everyone,
do you know
what we are doing today?
To accelerate the Jianmu Tree's growth
and rebuild the heavenly ladder.
More than that.
To reorganize the Twelve Immortal Sects
and rebuild the immortal order.
Not just that either.
In ancient times,
Pangu separated heaven and earth,
divided the Yin and Yang of the world,
and distinguished heaven and earth.
Then,
the Dao of Heaven
nurtured spiritual energy,
bestowed brilliance upon all things,
and enlightened all sentient beings.
After that,
gods descended to the world
to rule the Three Realms.
Nuwa and Fuxi created the Human Race.
But what about us cultivators?
We consider ourselves
to be of human origin,
but we are no longer human.
We have cultivated hard
for thousands of years,
only to find that
the path to Ascension is broken.
We can't become gods,
nor can we be human.
We are left in the mortal realm,
accused of preying on the common people.
We want Ascension,
but there is no way out.
But logically,
shouldn't we be
next to the gods
as the elites of this world?
Shouldn't we have
a great achievement recorded in history?
I want to open the heavenly ladder
and take back everything
that rightfully belongs to us.
Everyone,
do you have any objections?
No objections.
I want to open the heavenly ladder
and rewrite history
for all cultivators,
and myself.
I want to seek a rightful
and bright future for us.
Everyone,
any objections?
We will follow
the Sect Leader to the death!
Open the heavenly ladder
and rebuild the heavenly path.
This action
will benefit cultivators
for generations to come.
Everyone.
The path to heaven
is destined to be difficult and dangerous.
I am also prepared
to sacrifice myself.
As long as
the Jianmu Heavenly Ladder is rebuilt,
this world will never lack
cultivators
in the Deity Transformation stage again.
Reopen the heavenly ladder!
Replant the Jianmu Tree.
Mo Guan,
fend off the enemy with your junior,
Cang Fengzi, here.
Fellow Taoist, Xia Xuanzi,
come with me to the Rainwatch Terrace.
It's my honor.
[Guiyuan Hall]
I look forward
to meeting you all
in the divine realm.
Farewell, Sect Leader.
Wishing the Sect Leader success
in rebuilding the heavenly ladder
and ascending to the highest heaven.
No more waiting.
Everyone,
follow me to attack Tianyuan Mountain!
Attack Tianyuan Mountain!
Attack!
Attack! Attack!
All disciples, listen to my command!
Yes!
Set up the Killing Formation
and defend the mountain gate to the death!
Defend the mountain gate to the death!
Please, fellow Taoist, protect us.
Fellow Taoist Xia,
do you remember that the Crazy Taoist
once made 2 prophecies?
First,
there will be a great calamity
in this world.
Second,
the person born on September 9th
is the savior of the world.
Do you believe it, fellow Taoist?
Do you believe it, Sect Leader Li?
I do.
The heavenly ladder is broken,
and the gods have left.
No one in the immortal sect
can ascend to the Heavenly Gate anymore.
This is
the great calamity.
Only the one who rebuilds
the heavenly ladder,
opens the passage between
humans and gods,
and carves out
a new path of life for this world
is the true savior of the world.
Isn't that referring
to me?
Today,
I will open this Heavenly Gate,
follow the destiny,
and resolve the predicament
of the severed connection to heaven.
I will relieve the predicament
of the people.
I will tear through the clouds
and ascend to the Ninth Realm!
I want to ask the gods in heaven
if they know
the prestige of us cultivators.
Oh no. We need to hurry.
How dare you use such cheap tricks
in front of my father?
Didn't you ask
who the ancestor of this formation is?
Break!
Daoist Master Gong Yu,
please take a trip with Bai.
Tell Li Mofu to get out here.
Three little mice escaped.
I'll be right back.
It's you.
Everyone, be careful.
Something is wrong with her.
You guys go first.
I'll deal with her.
Be careful.
Let's go.
The feeling of having power
is truly wonderful.
You even stuff your mouths
with things refined from
the immortal perception
of your fellow sect members.
Can't believe that trash like you
dare to call yourselves an orthodox sect
and the head of the Twelve Immortal Sects.
It seems the golden liquid
can only strengthen the body,
but not the brain.
Han, be careful!
Young Master Lin.
It's been a while,
but you've barely improved.
You are all here.
Where is Lu Qianqiao?
Grandmaster.
A heart has 9 apertures.
Qian, Kan, Gen, Zhen, Zhong,
Xun, Li, Kun, and Dui.
Opening all nine apertures
forms the null heart,
making one a god who can
command the wind and rain,
and move mountains and seas,
Opening six apertures
forms the Earthly Heart,
making one a War Demon with
extraordinary combat power
and an exceptionally sturdy body.
Opening three apertures
forms the hearts of men,
making one ordinary in this world,
living among all beings.
The more apertures you open,
the stronger your ability to communicate
with heaven and earth becomes.
The speed of absorbing spiritual energy
also becomes faster.
The innate Earthly Heart
with six open apertures
is also the source of the bloodline power
of the War Demons.
The last step for you to turn from
a War Demon
into an ordinary human
is to borrow
the power of the Crimson Flame
from the Lantern Dragon Grass to seal the
Zhen, Zhong, and Xun apertures
in the Earthly Heart.
This will completely dissolve and seal
the bloodline,
leaving only the mortal heart's
Li, Kun, and Dui apertures open.
You will maintain vitality like a mortal.
From now on,
you will not be burdened by the curse.
But just like a normal person,
you will experience birth, aging,
illness, and death.
Later,
I will open your chest
to seal the apertures.
This process is unbearably painful.
Please, Grandmaster,
drink this bowl of Anesthesia Brew.
When you wake up,
your wish will be fulfilled,
and you will become a true mortal.
Undress Grandmaster.
Yes.
Grandmaster.
I knew you'd come here.
You traitor.
Don't you have any gratitude
for the Sect?
I just despise being associated with you.
That's because you're useless now.
You can't cultivate the great Dao
or ascend to heaven and become a god.
You have no choice but to
side with mortals
and beg for mercy.
If you know what's good for you,
stay far away,
and you might be able
to live for a few more years.
It's a pity
you chose the wrong path
and came to the wrong place.
You think the path you chose is right?
Of course.
Spawning the Jianmu Tree
to ascend to heaven
requires absorbing massive vitality
indiscriminately,
starting from the nearest source.
You look like you're destined
for a short life.
Who's to say you won't be chosen
by the Jianmu Tree,
drained of your vitality,
and have your Dao perish,
ultimately becoming nourishment
for the Jianmu Tree,
and a stepping stone for others?
This is gambling with my life. If I win,
I'll ascend to godhood,
live as long as the heaven and earth,
and enjoy endless fortune and prosperity.
Isn't such a rare opportunity
worth
risking everything
for a gamble?
Even if you want to gamble,
you don't get the chance.
Bai Zongying,
actually, I've always looked down on you.
You were able to become a Heavenly Talent
because you had good luck,
chose the right day,
and became
the Sect Leader's disciple by luck.
In the past, you were imposing,
powerful,
and amazing.
You always had to be one step ahead of me.
And now?
You're useless.
Your luck has run out.
Now I am an immortal,
and you are a mortal.
I said you can't pass,
so you must die right here.
Before the God-Demon War,
the heavenly ladder was always there.
But how many people in this world
could attain the Dao, ascend,
and become an immortal?
How long have you been in the sect?
You're older than I am
and have cultivated longer than I have.
But why am I the senior,
and you the junior?
Because he is dull-witted
and has poor aptitude.
All these years,
relying on the Yangyuan Pills
and the Qinghong Sect's
shady deals,
you barely managed to elevate
your cultivation
to the Nascent Soul stage.
Do you really think that makes you
comparable to my Senior Bai now?
An ignorant
and arrogant piece of trash like you,
copying others
and dreaming of ascending to heaven.
What a joke.
If I hadn't refused to
collude with Master,
you wouldn't have been
included in his plans.
Can Yangyuan Pills and
the Qinghong Sect's golden liquid
help you achieve Deity Transformation?
Even if the path to heaven
is placed right in front of you,
can you step onto it?
Sima Randeng,
who exactly gave you the courage
to bark and rave here
despite being an oblivious fool?
Attack!
Kill them!
Senior Bai,
you go up first.
Junior.
Senior Bai,
no matter what you do,
I will always follow you.
But this time,
I hope you can listen to me.
As long as I don't die today,
no one will get up the mountain.
Senior!
Then I'll kill you first,
and then him.
How come I never realized before
that I was this strong?
I just took on 10 of them at once.
That's because
I was holding them off at the front.
Lord of Rust-Sword,
are you interested
in joining our Lingji Mountain?
I'll reward you with the
Protector Elder title for the thrills.
Get lost.
Lions don't play with dogs.
That's the rule.
I won't allow you
to insult yourself like that.
Where is Li Mofu?
Tell that old mutt to come see me!
You overestimated yourself.
Greetings, Senior Xia Xuanzi.
Cast with all your might!
It's done.
It's done!
Old mutt, damn you!
Han...
Father!
Han... Han.
I won't accept this...
Jing...
Cook!
Senior Xia Xuanzi.
Your power is boundless.
What's happening?
I won the bet! I'm not dead!
Thank you, Patriarch, for your protection.
Since I'm not dead,
the ones who should die next
are you!
This is fate.
Father.
Father...
Fellow cultivators,
Tianyuan is unjust.
We have no way out.
We either die fighting,
or fight to the death!
Kill!
Lin Muhan, pull yourself together!
Get up quickly!
Lin Muhan!
Kill...
Advancing to the Nascent Soul stage
on the spot?
Kill!
Bai Zongying.
You've lost your immortal perception.
Have you lost your mind, too?
The Infinity Bell
is forged from
Jiuli Red Fire Refined Copper.
Only cultivators at or above
the Nascent Soul stage
can activate it.
As a piece of trash
who lost his immortal perception,
what will you use to activate
the Mountain-Guarding Formation?
With your miserable life?
Senior Bai!
Oh no!
Stop right there!
Come back!
You are no match for him!
Bai Zongying,
are you crazy?
You are asking for death!
♪ Caught in fate's design,
I search my soul ♪
♪ What should I do to avoid
living my life in vain? ♪
You're still young.
♪ My blade stays clean,
untouched by dust ♪
Why do you want to join
our Tianyuan Sect?
♪ Yet it's sparked thousands of wars ♪
There is a prophecy
that a great calamity
will befall the world.
A person born on September 9th
♪ A towering tree worn down into
a blade devoid of feeling ♪
will become the savior of the world.
I was born on September 9th.
♪ The heart hides its root
at the bottom of the abyss ♪
♪ In red, I look at you
with a glimpse of shame ♪
So you think
you are that savior of the world?
I... I don't know.
But if I have the chance,
♪ Being haunted by the spell,
even if it's cruel ♪
I hope I am.
Saving the world could mean suffering.
♪ It's better than being trapped by fate ♪
You might get hurt, bleed,
♪ Between gain and loss ♪
or even lose your life.
♪ Lies a thousand years of grace ♪
Aren't you afraid?
I'm not afraid.
Why not?
Sacrifice oneself to defend the Dao,
and face death fearlessly.
♪ Even if it's soul-eroding,
collarbone-binding pain, I accept it all ♪
♪ Let strong wine carry me into
drunken nights till midnight ♪
♪ Let my soul blaze in brilliant colors ♪
♪ Let the agony of a thousand cuts ♪
♪ Stand as proof that I have lived ♪
♪ Let me taste a life of flesh and blood
in full ♪
♪ Let me savor the many flavors
of the mortal world ♪
♪ Let me face the world's
warmth and cold alike ♪
♪ To live and perish with it,
daring to go mad, daring to dream ♪
Senior Bai!
♪ Don't live in vain,
have a pleasant journey of life ♪
♪ Caught in fate's design,
I search my soul ♪
♪ What should I do to avoid
living my life in vain? ♪
♪ My blade stays clean,
untouched by dust ♪
♪ Yet it's sparked thousands of wars ♪
♪ Even if it's soul-eroding,
collarbone-binding pain, I accept it all ♪
♪ Embracing pain as home,
reborn like a phoenix ♪
♪ Just to trade the rest of my days
for one true life as a human ♪
♪ Let strong wine carry me into
drunken nights till midnight ♪
♪ Let my soul blaze in brilliant colors ♪
♪ Let the agony of a thousand cuts ♪
I'll leave things here to you.
♪ Stand as proof that I have lived ♪
♪ Let me taste a life of flesh and blood
in full ♪
♪ Let me savor the many flavors
of the mortal world ♪
♪ Let me face the world's
warmth and cold alike ♪
♪ To live and perish with it,
daring to go mad, daring to dream ♪
♪ Let strong wine carry me into
drunken nights till midnight ♪
♪ Let my soul blaze in brilliant colors ♪
♪ Let the agony of a thousand cuts ♪
♪ Stand as proof that I have lived ♪
♪ Let me taste a life of flesh and blood
in full ♪
♪ Let me savor the many flavors
of the mortal world ♪
♪ Let me face the world's
warmth and cold alike ♪
♪ To live and perish with it,
daring to go mad, daring to dream ♪
♪ Don't live in vain,
have a pleasant journey of life ♪